Danial Waheed

Peshawar District, Khyber Pakhtunkhwa, Pakistan



daniyalwahied@gmail.com



03169188719



linkedin.com/in/danial-waheed

Summary

A front-end developer with more than 3 years of experience in projects of varying complexity following modern web development practices and new technologies.

Expertise are focused on HTML5, CSS3, SaaS, Bootstrap ,JavaScript, React Js, GIT and responsive design/ coding.

I am interested in teams valuing quality, clean code, principles & testing.

Experience



Freelance Frontend Developer

Freelance

Jan 2020 - Present (2 years 6 months +)

Freelance Graphic Designer

Self-employed

May 2019 - Sep 2021 (2 years 5 months)

Education



Abbottabad University Of Science And Technology

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science 2019 - 2023

Licenses & Certifications

- (A) Responsive Web Design freeCodeCamp
- **Learn HTML Course** Codecademy
- **CSS Course** Codecademy
- Intermediate CSS Course Codecademy
- Responsive Design Course Codecademy

- **Learn Navigation Design Course** Codecademy
- **Color Design Course** Codecademy
- **Bootstrap Course** Codecademy
- JavaScript Course Codecademy
- (A) JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures freeCodeCamp
- Front-End Web Developer LinkedIn
 Certificate Id: AW4j-K8dK1TAMj9GE7w5fS8Lqaoa

Skills

React.js • Front-End Development • JavaScript • HTML • CSS • Web Design • Git • Responsive Web Design